# Luc Tan Do

### Business Analyst/Scrum Master

An experienced and highly skilled Business Analyst with a strong track record of delivering successful projects and driving business process improvements for the past 3 years. A versatile professional who excels in collaborating with cross-functional teams, including business users, project managers, and development teams, to define project objectives and deliverables. A proactive and detailoriented professional, constantly seeking opportunities to optimize processes, increase efficiency, and achieve business goals. Dedicated to staying updated with the latest IT industry trends and advancements to continuously contribute towards the success of IT projects.

dotanluc1301@gmail.com



0838327414



P Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam



github.com/dotanluc1301

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Business Analyst/Scrum Master** bravoSUITE - Orient Software

06/2022 - 09/2023

bravoSUITE strives to be the all-encompassing ERP system that provides a full cycle of intelligent HR and personnel management solutions for the company.

#### Responsibilities

- Host and facilitate workshops and Scrum events.
- Inspect the market and contribute to the creation of the product master plan.
- Manage features in each application's unique version and serve as the point of contact for customers (Vietnamese, Norwegian, and Japanese) and the product team.
- Gather and document business needs and translate them into functional specifications.
- Support the Product Owner to conduct regular meetings with the development teams to review progress, provide clarification on requirements, maintain the product roadmap, and ensure successful delivery.
- Work closely with the development team to ensure requirements alignment and successful implementation.

### Developer

**CICAT - BOSCH** 

03/2019 - 05/2022

CI-CAT is a GUI desktop application circulated within the enterprise that provides end-users with a handy set of controls that manage BOSCH global domain resources (e-mail, user account, etc ...) by connection to Active Directory Domain Services and Exchange Server.

### Responsibilities

- Implement new features and fix the existing defects.
- Take part in analysing requirements and eliciting the needs of stakeholders through open points.
- Provide remote technical support to customers via e-mail and Q&A meeting sessions.
- Manage and create release details on business documents.

## **EDUCATION**

#### Study Program

Ho Chi Minh City Univercity of Foreign Languages - Information Technology

2016 - 2020

2.99 (system 4)

Information Technology

Software Engineering

### **SKILLS**



### CERTIFICATES

EF SET English Certificate (04/2024)

- 72/100 (C2 Proficient based on the EF SET score scale )
- Issued by EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

Professional Scrum Master II (03/2024)

- Issued by Scrum.org

Professional Scrum Product Owner I (01/2024)

Issued by Scrum.org

Professional Scrum Master I (01/2024)

Issued by Scrum.org

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Full Professional Proficiency

### **TOOLS**

